Life is how you live it... not how you spend it.
The Ultimate Gift is a romance, drama, family
film directed by Michael O. Sajbel.
When his wealthy grandfather finally dies, Jason Stevens fully expects
to benefit when it comes to the reading of the will.
But instead of a sizable inheritance, Jason receives a test, a series
of tasks he must complete before he can get any money.
Jason Stevens, played by Drew Fuller.
Emily Rose, played by Abigail Breslin.
Howard 'Red' Stevens, played by James Garner.
Ted Hamilton, played by Bill Cobbs.
Alexia, played by Ali Hillis.
Miss Hastings, played by Lee Meriwether.
The Ultimate Gift is a 2006 American drama film directed by Michael O.
Sajbel from a screenplay written by Cheryl McKay, which is
based on the best selling novel by Jim Stovall.
The author cameos in the film.
It stars Drew Fuller, Bill Cobbs, Lee Meriwether, Ali Hillis, Abigail Breslin,
Brian Dennehy, and James Garner (in his final live action film).
It was released on March 9, 2007, in the United States and Canada.
Two sequels to the film, The Ultimate Life and The Ultimate
Legacy, were released in 2013 and 2017 respectively.
The film explores themes of grandparent grandchild
relationship, leukemia, wealth, cancer, inheritance.
The tone is emotional.